You're on your own.
If I die young, bury me in lay me down.
The roses take me in a river and don't
send me away.
Rainbow Shin
knows
I die young. Bury me in sat. Lay me
down. The roses take me in the river.
And don't send me away.
Lord, make me a rainbow. Shine out on my
mother. She know I'm safe with you. She
stands under my color. Oh, heat, heat.
Yeah. Heat.
Heat.
Sometimes you just want to scream.
Sometimes you just got to scream.
Sometimes you just got to shout. You
just got to say
Heat up
here.
Sometimes I walk along the only road.
Heat. Heat.
Yeah.
Heat.
All of the night.
Oh, that's a pretty good song. Oh my
god.
Are you blaring this through the
apartment?
Yeah. Hell yeah I am. Hell yeah I am. My
I'm just I'm disturbing my neighbors
with this as much as I can. I'm
disturbing the whole entire neighborhood
with this. I promise you. I promise you.
You brought this to you. You brought
this. You brought this. You want
disturbance in the world. You want pain.
You want suffering. You want noise.
You want suicide. You want death. You
want destruction. You shall have it.
You will have it.
The once you've knest me is dead. You
get a new person.
on mirales.
We're bleeding
You're bleeding out.
like cake in a crisis
crisis.
We're bleeding out
for you
to
rain.
body
and talk like Jesus.
Try walk like Jesus.
Talk like Jesus.
Like Jesus
like Jesus.
Some This song,
my bounce, my dick, my bounce, my
love, how you like this
works.
Works is
like Jesus.
Try walking like Jesus.
Sit and talk like Jesus.
Try walking like a Jesus.
in the wind.
Try lifting the star.
Try extending your hand.
Get the [__] out of my way.
Who's the aggressive ones? They've been
stuck me for 8 months. This is my only
moment I get to react to this [__]
insanity.
Heat.
Oh. Oh, my balls. Oh, my dick. Oh, my
dick feels so good. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh, my
dick. Oh, my dick. Ah.
Heat
up here.
Heat.
[__] the neighbors. [__] the neighbors.
[__] life. [__] society. [__] police.
[__] everything. [__] society. [__]
everything. [__] everything. [__]
people.
What of the pious,
pure of heart, the peaceful,
what are the me,
the morning, and merciful.
All
adore.
Heat
up
here.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Heat. Heat.
I can look into where your soul used to
be and there's nothing. There's just a
gaping old madness.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.
Yeah.
Heat.
soon
into each other.
Lift on higher.
can never win.
How can How How can you win when you're
only losing?
Hello, Crystal Mist. What's up? How you
doing? How you doing? How you doing? How
you doing? You want to see my dick?
Here's my dick. You want to see? Oh. Oh,
my pants. My dick is right here. You
want to Oh, I'm grabbing my dick. It's
right here. Oh. Oh. Oh.
You need
a voice and home of many
You think I'm highly inappropriate?
Have you take a look at your own life?
Have you take a look at your own [__]
life
stream?
I'm showing you my bulge to everyone.
You want to see my bulge? You want to
see my [__] bulge? Here's my bulge.
M
ah
does that bother you?
Does that bother you? Huh?
I don't
want to see you.
I
love you.
When you
down
too will go to death. You too will go to
Satan. You will be one of Satan's
children at the afterlife. In the
afterlife, you will be one of Satan's
children. Mark my words.
If there is a Satan and there is a God.
You want more content? Give me some more
up votes.
Here's here's a tribute to all the
downers. This This one This one's a
tribute for you. Here you go. This one's
for you guys.
What's the matter?
Did you prove it yet? Did you prove it?
You [__] [__] Did you prove it? I
guess you didn't. I guess you just
figured it. I am the center of the
universe. I am God. I am your God.
I am the one that decides the winds, the
fires, and everything else
from the creation to the end. I am the
one that did all of this. Nothing came
before me and nothing will come after me
because after me there is nothing. It's
the end of the line for humanity, for
all of the world. When you say you live
13 whatever [__] billion years or
trillions of years, I don't give a [__]
because before my life there was
nothing. You can't even prove it. You
can't even prove it. Even if you can't
even prove it, even if you say your life
was there, it was all a [__]
simulation.
Cuz all
around me and everything you do depends
on me and everything.
I am the center of this.
I am
creat
you think I will forget You think I
remember? I remember you. I remember
you. I see everything you do.
Just wait till I return to the
afterlife.
So good.
Maybe you'll burn eternal fire. Maybe
I'll make sure your punishment will be.
Maybe I am God. Maybe I'm your God.
What's going
on?
What you doing? Oh [__]
in this life.
You don't feel
nothing for one second project in
project.
It's truly you looking at it's truly
your mirror that you're watching.
It's truly you that are projecting, not
me.
You get that?
You get that I see right through you
everything you do.
You get that I am the center of the
universe. You are nothing. You're
nothing to me.
None of you are nothing to me. Any you
don't mean anything to me.
Yes. You
Yeah. Yeah. You don't mean anything to
me. You're nothing.
But you did.
I will get back at you. God will get
back at you. God aka me. Doesn't matter.
Doesn't make a [__] difference. This
is all a [__] simulation. I am the
center of your [__] errors. Prove me
wrong. You can't.
I'm not God. Prove me wrong. Prove me
wrong. Prove me wrong. If I'm not your
God, why the [__] do you kneel down to
me? Why the [__] do you spend time here
if I'm not your God?
I don't give a [__] I don't give a [__]
what I am. Do you think I give a [__]
about what I say? What I do? Do you
think I
Do you think I actually give a [__]
What makes you think I give a [__]
What makes you think I actually give a
[__] [__] about you? About your
insignificant shitty life?
All you do is bring me words. Words of
what? Words of hurt and deceit.
Do you think I give a [__] about that?
Do you think God gives a [__] about
that? Do you think God gives a [__]
about your shitty words?
No. Nobody gives a [__]
put something real into the world, maybe
God will give a [__]
God is not impressed with you. God is
disappointed in all of you. He wants you
all to [__] die. All humanity, he
wants it to rot into hell. Why? Why?
Why? Because you're [__] You don't
deserve life. You don't deserve this
paradise. You don't deserve anything.
You deserve hell on earth. That's what
you're creating.
You don't create nothing good.
You create nothing. You create hell. You
create bad. And from this creation, you
get bad. You get the hell you deserve.
You You ask yourself, "Oh, what is
earth? Oh, what is hell? What is heaven?
What is all of this?" Well, you creating
it right now. This is it. This reality
is hell or heaven. You decide. What do
you want? You want hell? We can go to
hell.
I'll be your [__] Satan.
I'll be your Satan.
I'll be your hell.
I'll be your God. Your merciful God.
What do you want? You want a little
piece of hell? Or you want a little
piece of heaven?
I'm the center of your [__] universe.
[__] world. Look at me. Look at me in
the eyes. I am the center of your
[__] universe. I don't know. You
can't [__] look away. You can't click
away. You're looking at this.
You can't even prove me wrong. You can't
even prove to me that I'm not the sensor
of the universe. So that means I am both
your Satan and your [__] God. Yeah.
Yeah. I decide where you go. I decide
everything for you and in your
afterlife. If you're going to treat me
bad, you're going to get to hell. You're
going to get everything.
I'll make sure everything aligns just
for you. Cuz this world, this universe
is perfect. It's perfect. Everything is
perfect. There's nothing that's wrong
with this universe. And there's
something wrong with you.
There's something wrong with you
cuz you judge. You clean your fingers.
You do your [__] little [__] You do
yourself [__] [__] You think God
doesn't see that?
You're so mistaken. It's in every
[__] book in this universe. This
reality you call reality in every
[__] book. It says right there on
page three. It says you
and I will be that hair for you. I'll be
that god for you cuz I'm the center of
the [__] universe. And if you can't
[__] deal with it, get the [__] out
of here. I don't give a [__] Then
you're going to miss me. Then you're
going to be like, "Wait, why is
everything else so [__] false?"
First, because I'm the only thing that's
real. I am the core. I'm the essence.
I'm the root.
And I will take you there. I will take
you wherever you want to go. Trust me,
you will be
whatever you want to be.
You have free will. You can do what you
want to do. I didn't say to you don't
thumb me down. I didn't say to you thumb
me up. Whatever. I didn't say anything
to you. I told you [__] thumb me
down. If you're going to thumb me down,
give me a million thumbs down.
You see if I am the center of the
universe or not. Cuz at the end of your
life, at the end of your life, there'll
be somebody there to pick you up. And
it'd be a surprise for you if it was me
to come and pick you up
and take you right to hell.
Then you knew you'd be [__] wouldn't
you?
Cuz you treat me so bad. You treat me so
bad. I'm a human being just like anybody
else.
You treat another human being bad.
Doesn't it say in the Bible, don't treat
your brother like that. Treat your
brother like a brother. Treat your
sister like a sister. What do you do?
What do you do? You treat your brother
like an
like [__] You treat your sister like
[__] You treat everyone like [__]
You do the opposite of what's in the
book
of what you've been told.
But for me,
you will not have for the rest of your
life. You will have a misery, but for
the eternity after that, I will have
power over you.
You don't think I see what you're doing?
You don't think God sees what you're
doing? Do you think even if I can see
it, you don't think God can see what
you're doing?
Are you really so stupid? Do you really
think this life is so insignificant? Do
you really think that you can do
whatever you want? Go ahead. Do it. Do
it. Do whatever you want. Thumb it down.
Give me some more thumbs down. Come on.
Challenge God. Challenge God. Do it.
Challenge God. You You know you want You
want to challenge God. Go and challenge
it. Challenge him right now. Give me
some more thumbs down. Challenge God
right now. That's what you're doing.
You are the one with Satan. I can do
that, too. Satan, God, it's one and the
same. Trust me, I'll take you right to
hell.
It's where you want a little piece of
hell every time. Yeah. You want your
life to be a little piece of hell.
and write on me all you want. You know
I'm the center. I am the one. I am the
zero. I am all of it. I am all. I am
none. I am hell. I am heaven. I am
Satan. I am God. I am your end. I am
your start. I'm the beginning. I'm the
end. I'm the Alpha and I'm the Omega.
You're right. Satan is just another de
Satan is just an a saturation of God.
Satan is just a bad side of God.
If you think that that Satan is
separated from God, it's no difference,
man.
But when you decide to reside with
Satan, you will get the part of Satan
you do you would never ask for. You'll
get this part. You get this for you. You
coming. It's coming for you. It's coming
for you. It's coming for you. Your evil
is coming for you.
Do you know what's coming for you?
Misery, pain, death.
Death.
Death
is coming for you.
Look around you. Look around you.
Death is everywhere. It's coming for
you. It's looking It's luring lurking in
the corners for you. You decide to be
with Satan.
You will get it. This universe is so
beautiful. It makes room for everybody.
You want to be here too. You are here
too. But you will get it. You'll get
every piece of Satan. Don't worry. I'll
be the eyes and ears of God.
You will get your time.
Heat. Heat.
My
wishes.
Kill the galato.
H the last
Fore! Foreign! Foreign!
Let's shoot the gelato.
Hard face attack.
Welcome to
Johnny.
Heat. Heat. N.
in my blood.
Let me get a gunshot.
Heat. Heat.
Can you give me more downloads? Is that
all you got? Is that all you got? Is
this all it? Is this it?
127 downloads? Come on, you [__]
Is that all you got? Is that all you
got? You don't even touch me. You don't
even [__] reach me. Give me a million
more. Maybe I'll respond to that.
I am the center of your universe. I am
your God. I am your Satan. I am your
everything. I am your center of your
universe.
You are nothing. You are just a passent.
You're just a passent. You're here to
entertain me. Your only purpose in life
is to feed into my life. This is your
only purpose in life. How does that make
you feel? Like you're just a subject to
me. You're just a little experiment of
me. I created you. I created you out of
nothing. Cuz you are nothing. You're
nothing to me.
I excel in you in every way. I am more
superior to you. I am intelligent. I am
superior to you in every way. I'm your
Satan. I'm your God. I'm your beginning
and I'm your end.
You [__] fans. Give me a million
dollars. Yeah. Give me a million more
dollars. Why won't you? Why won't you
give me a million more dollars, you
little [__]
Is that all you got? 32 dislikes. Is
that all you got? Give me some more, you
[__] [__]
Prove to me I'm your god. Prove to me I
decide your world. I decide everything.
I say I want downloads, you give it to
me. You come give it to me. You come
give me those downloads
just like you want. Yeah.
Prove to me I'm your god.
You come
to me and your dislikes. All you do is
kneel to me. Cuz all you do you little
peasant. Peasant. You're a peasant. You
kneel to me. You kneel to me.
You're my peasant. You're my slave.
You're my property.
You're mine.
I'm your god.
I'm your universe. I'm the center of
this.
You're nothing.
Nothing. You're absolutely nothing.
Nobody cares about you.
You're the center of the universe.
>> Really wants me to talk with him. Well,
does he think he can offer me? Does he
offer me anything? Does he offer me
does he offer me
consolidation?
Does he offer me relief of this pain,
this misery, and this torture? Does he
offer me relief from this? Or does he
just offer me more pain and suffering?
Because this cog,
why should I talk with him? He's just a
peasant. It's not a peasant to me. Just
like any of the all of they're all
peasants. They're all peasants. You're
all peasants to me. I am God. You should
kneel down and bow before me.
Who's this cog?
K is nothing to me. Just like you are
all nothing to me.
Get this [__] take this. Take this
torture, you piece of shits. Take this
torture. Take this. Enjoy this. If you
don't enjoy this, I hope you get
tortured by this.
You know the rules.
He cannot make $1,000 of my content. If
he can, good, good, good on him, man.
Dude, if you can make a $1,000 of my
content, dude. It just proves that I am
God. I am the source. I am the one. I'm
the zero. I am the alpha and the omega.
I am the world. I am the center of this
universe. And nobody can prove me wrong.
I am God.
You try to kill me. You try to murder
me. You try to take me from this earth,
but you cannot.
You see, I am God. And I'll put my mercy
on you. I'll put my hatred on you. And
I'll put my wrath on you.
You think you can escape my [__]
judgment?
No, you cannot. You cannot. You will be
found. God will find you.
I'm just kidding.
all you can do 100 I'm like what is this
157 dislikes? Is that all you can do?
Is that all you have?
Is that all you can do? 157 dislikes.
You can't give me a million dislikes.
What's wrong with you? Why are you so
weak? You're so weak. You're so weak.
This is all you got? This is all the
hatred you have for me.
Give me some more. Give me some more.
Give me some more hatred. Come on. Give
me all your hatred. Why don't you have
more for me? 157. I'm so disappointed in
you.
You're so weak. You're so weak. You're
so
weak.
157. You're nothing. You're nothing.
Give me another. Give me 158. You don't
have more than 157 dislikes for me. Come
on. Give me more.
Give me more. Give me more.
Come on, you [__]
Today I want your dislikes. And this is
all you give me? 157.
I'm your God. I'm the center of your
universe and you give me 157.
God is disappointed in you. Satan is
disappointed in you.
You can't even live up to Satan's
request. Give me a million dislikes. If
you like Satan, give me a million
dislikes. Give me a million. Huh? You
like Satan so much. Why don't you give
me a million dislikes or four more
dislikes? 10 more dislikes. That's all
you got, Satan. Come on.
Come on. You don't scare me. You're
nothing to me. You're nothing. You're
nothing.
You're insignificant.
Your contribution to this world is
insignificant.
Insignificant.
You're just a little speck. Just a
little speck. Just a little pause.
I'm here to take all this hatred.
Suck it in. Give me more. Give me some
more. Why can't you give me more? This
is all you got. This is all the hatred
you have for me. This is all.
This is all. 189 dislikes. That's
nothing. That's nothing. Give me a mill.
I told you. Give me a million and you
are stuck at 189. A
That's all you got. Oh.
Oh.
You're so weak. You're so weak. You're
so weak.
I am in your command. I control you.
Give me some more dislikes.
Please,
please. Come on. Give me some more.
I am.
I control you. Come on. Come on.
You're so bad.
You're so bad. I got you. I got you.
Around my little finger. Around my
little finger. That's where I have you.
My little finger. You know what this
little finger did?
You know what this little finger did?
This little finger did get you.
Give me another dislike.
Come on. You know you want to. You know
you want to. You know you want to make
another account. Give me another
dislike.
Bow down to me. Kneel to me. Give me
another dislike.
Give it to me. Come on. Give it to me.
Give it. Give me another dislike. You
just give me one because of that speech.
Just one dislike. Come on. Give me
another one.
Prove to me I am in your control. I'm in
your command.
You bow down to me. You kneel to me.
Give me another dislike. Give me more
dislikes. All the people that dislike,
you are kneeling to me. You're in my
command. This is what I want from you.
You're giving it to me. You're giving me
the power. You're giving me the power.
The power. The power you want. You're
giving it to me.
You're giving it to me.
I'm your God. I'm your Satan.
You decide what I can be. I could be
your God. I could be your Satan.
I'll be your Satan for downloads. No
problem. I'll be your Satan. You need
Satan in your life. I thought you need
God. I thought you needed Jesus. But you
need Satan. You need to have the end
coming for you.